picchore.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy | Pic Chore

## Privacy

Posted On: July 22, 2010  

Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access Picchore (“PICCHORE”). Your use of PICCHORE indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

 **Information Collection** ****  
PICCHORE is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. PICCHORE may collect information from our users at several different points on the site.

 **Comments** ****  
In order to enhance their use of PICCHORE, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Commenters may register anonymously. However, if a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Service (e.g. libels them), then in accordance with our Terms, we will make reasonable efforts to contact the commenter and alert them to the situation. If we are required to by law to disclose commenters’ contact information, we will attempt to contact commenters to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our Terms of Use for more information.

 **Mailing Lists** ****  
PICCHORE may launch a mailing list fin order to provide subscribers with relevant information – breaking news, or weekly or daily round-ups, for example. In order to sign up to receive regular emails, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from PICCHORE. Most of the time, these will be content from PICCHORE, but we may occasionally send out an email from a third party sponsor. This will be infrequent, and does not represent an endorsement by PICCHORE of any products advertised therein. It will clearly be marked as advertising.

 **Third Party Cookies** ****  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, PICCHORE has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by PICCHORE only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Advertising**  
Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about users’ visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve Google ads to users on this site.

 **Links** ****  
PICCHORE contains links to other sites. Please be aware that PICCHORE is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by PICCHORE.

 **Log Files** ****  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Business Transitions** ****  
In the event PICCHORE goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

 **Legal Disclaimer** ****  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, PICCHORE may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on PICCHORE.

 **Notification of Changes** ****  
Whenever Picchore changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact jerod@orangecaster.com, or by mail to Picchore, 13601 Preston Road – Carillon Towers 250E, Dallas, TX, 75240.
